<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".securityandprivacy">

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="1dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="1dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="1dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="1dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="1.0"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="1.0">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_height="match_parent">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView16"
                android:layout_width="359dp"
                android:layout_height="799dp"
                android:paddingStart="5dp"
                android:text="Data Encryption: Encrypt sensitive user data both in transit and at rest using strong encryption algorithms. This includes user credentials, payment information, and any other personally identifiable information (PII).  Secure Authentication: Use secure authentication mechanisms such as OAuth or JWT to authenticate users securely. Implement strong password policies, multi-factor authentication (MFA), and session management to prevent unauthorized access.  User Privacy Controls: Provide users with granular privacy controls to manage their personal information, including profile details, location data, and ride history. Allow users to opt-in or opt-out of data collection and sharing.  Secure Communication: Use HTTPS for all communication between the app and the server to prevent eavesdropping and man-in-the-middle attacks. Implement certificate pinning to verify the authenticity of the server.  Data Minimization: Collect and store only the minimum amount of data necessary for app functionality. Regularly review and delete outdated or unnecessary user data to reduce the risk of data breaches.  Payment Security: Integrate a secure payment gateway to handle financial transactions securely. Follow industry standards such as PCI DSS compliance to protect users' payment card data.  Location Privacy: Implement strong privacy controls for location data, allowing users to choose when and how their location is shared. Use anonymization techniques to protect user identity in location-based services.  Security Testing: Conduct regular security assessments, including penetration testing and code reviews, to identify and address security vulnerabilities proactively. Implement secure coding practices and adhere to security standards and guidelines.  Data Encryption: Encrypt sensitive data such as user credentials, payment details, and communication channels to protect them from unauthorized access.  Compliance: Ensure compliance with relevant privacy regulations such as GDPR, CCPA, and HIPAA, depending on the geographic location and nature of the data collected."
                android:textSize="24sp" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>